Stop prompting Claude. Andre Garpathy
thinks there's a much better way to work
with AI. And his method has three
layers. Layer one is the spec. Instead
of giving Claude a task and hoping it
understands you, work with it to create
a detailed spec first. Have Claude
interview you about what you're actually
trying to achieve, then break the work
into smaller checkpoints before it
starts. So, Nvidia just made building
with AI basically free. They're giving
developers free API access to over 80 AI
models. Here's how you use it. Go to
Nvidia, choose the model you want, and
generate an API key. [music] You can
choose from models like Kimmy, GLM,
Deepseek, and loads more. So, you want
to start a real business, but you can't
afford people for content, marketing,
sales, and all the other types of work
yet because you can now install AI
agents for free. One to help create
content, one to help follow up with
leads, and other types of agents to help
handle the jobs that your first
employees normally would do for you.
Isn't it crazy that with just my natural
language, I can get all of these crazy
motion graphics right here, and I can
get all of these insane animations over
here as well. I can have subtitles
appearing at the bottom, like you see. I
can take my face, and I can put it in
the bottom right corner, or I can bring
it up to the top left corner. And I can
even play you guys clips of a bunch of
my different YouTube videos right here
in this sort of 3D fashion. So by the
end of this video, you will know exactly
how to actually do this, even if you've
never really used codec before or you've
never edited videos before. So I don't
want to waste any of your time. Let's
just get straight into this video. All
right, so I hope you guys are excited to
learn how to do this. What you're going
to need is you're going to need the
Codex desktop app and you're going to
need to install Hyperframes. But I'm
going to show you guys all that. Before
we go through the setup, I just wanted
to show you a few examples of how I've
been using it and the skills that I'm
going to give you guys for completely
free. So this first example is just
having it help me edit YouTube videos
because what it's able to do is it
transcribes the audio and then it can
cut out mistakes and stutters and things
like that and you know dead space. So
for example in this one I gave it two
different recordings. I gave it my face
cam and I gave it my screen recording.
And this was a 14-minute video that got
cut down to 9 minutes and now it has
like the background and it also has a
few cuts. So let me just show you what I
mean by that. So here's the video. It's
not live yet but this is how it starts
off. Today I'm going over the 18 core C
codeex concepts that you actually need
to know in order to start using it right
away and getting value from it. It
doesn't matter if you're not technical
at all or you've never used codeex
before. By the end of this video you'll
understand exactly how this thing
actually works so that you can start
using it right away. So as you can see
that first animation with the 18 cards
coming into the screen that was
hyperframes as well as you know codecs
here driving the actual edits, the
rounded crops, the background, all of
this. And so part one we're going to
start off here is foundations. So we're
going to kick off with concept number
one which is projects. Now a lot of you
guys I'm assuming have used chatbt or
claude in the now all of that logic was
once again hyperframes. It basically
created the card that said you know
number one projects. It then decided to
also zoom me in here because it realizes
that for the next you know 10 to 15
seconds I might be talking about
something but I'm not showing anything
on screen. So, I prompted it in this way
and I gave it the skills in this way to
understand that when there's nothing
going on on the screen, maybe you do a
full screen, but then when it's time to
do more of a tutorial, you go back into
this view. So, anyways, throughout this
whole video, that's basically what it
does. It's able to jump between full
screen and this basically, you know,
template or scene and then it also
creates those cards in between each of
the concepts. There is like a transition
screen. All right, so that's one quick
example. Let's take a look at some short
form content which I think is getting
much much better. So, here I have it
doing two reels. One is about Claude and
one is about Nvidia. So, let me just
real quick play these two for you and
then we'll break them down. Stop
prompting Claude. Andre Karpathy thinks
there's a much better way to work with
AI. And his method has three layers.
Layer one is the spec. Instead of giving
Claude a task and hoping it understands
you, work with it to create a detailed
spec first. Have Claude interview you
about what you're actually trying to
achieve. Then break the work into
smaller checkpoints before it starts.
Layer two is the verifier. Before Claude
does anything, define exactly what a
good result looks like. Then give it
ways to actually check its own work.
Whether that's another AI model or real
data or tests that it can run on its
own. And layer three is the environment.
Build a workspace where Claude already
has your instructions, your knowledge,
your skills, and your rules every single
time you use it. So instead of becoming
better at writing prompts, you're
building an entire system around Claude
that makes it better every [music] time
you use it. I made a full YouTube video
breaking down Karpathy's method and
exactly how to build this yourself. So
just comment method and I'll send it to
you. So Nvidia just made building with
AI basically free. They're giving
developers free API access to over 80 AI
models. Here's how you use it. Go to
Nvidia, choose the model you want, and
generate an API key. [music] You can
choose from models like Kimmy, GLM,
Deepseek, and loads more. Then take that
key and plug it directly into whatever
you're building with, so you can
experiment with AI apps, automations,
and other projects without immediately
racking up API costs. And because
they're OpenAI compatible APIs, you can
use them with loads of existing AI
workflows. If you wanted to start
building with AI, but didn't want to
burn your own money testing different
models, this makes it way easier. So
just comment key and I'll send you the
full setup. So I thought that those
outputs were really, really solid. You
can see that what it does is it kind of
starts off with like a visual hook. I
guess we'll go to the clawed one first.
We have the three missing pieces and
what it did here is it's kind of
creating that open loop because it's
saying, "Hey, yeah, you know, Andre
Carpathy uses it in this way and it's
creating this open loop of, oh wow, I
need to stay to the end of this short to
see what all three of these are."
Because as we go through, we can see we
have number one. We could talk about
little number one and then we go into
number two, the verifier. And then we
get into number three finally at the
end, which is about the environment. And
so about every one or two seconds here,
it's switching. You know, we've got some
scenes where it's like this with B-roll
up top and me down here. It's got some
where it's a full screen animation. It's
got some where it's full screen me. And
all these animations are sort of like
paper style. There's texture. It's 3D.
They're always moving. So, we're never
having one element be still. You've also
noticed that it went out and it got all
of this B-roll. It either created it or
it recorded it itself. And the
subtitles, it was made by Hyperframes
and Astra. The music, the sound effects,
all of this is being synced to the
actual reel for engagement. And pretty
much same thing with the Nvidia one.
This one was shorter, but it's a similar
style. This one has more green accents
rather than orange because it's about
Nvidia, but it has the same types of
animations. It has the same types of,
you know, scenes, and it has the same
way that it's fast-paced. It's always
switching. We have music. We have real
B-roll that it went out and it collected
on its own. And here's even more AI
generated B-roll that it created on its
own. I think that this is getting
really, really good. And I've turned
this into a skill. And like I said, all
of these are skills that come inside of
one sort of student kit is what I'm
calling it. So, if you want to get it
all for free, just go into my free
school community. The link for that is
down in the description. And then you're
going to go to the classroom and you'll
go to either AI skills or all YouTube
resources. I have it linked in a bunch
of spots, so it's really easy to find,
but you'll be able to find it right in
here in the AI skills section. It'll be
called like hyperframes student kit.
Here's another quick example. This one
is an AIS reel, and it made this one for
me in both um 16x9 as well as 9x6. But
let me just real quick play the 9x6
version for you guys because it's kind
of like a reel, but it's a little bit
different cuz this one was meant to be
an ad. What if you could build the team
before you hired it? So, you want to
start a real business, but you can't
afford people for content, marketing,
sales, and all the other types of work
yet? Because you can now install AI
agents for free. One to help create
content, one to help follow up with
leads, and other types of agents to help
handle the jobs that your first
employees normally would do for you.
It's like building your first AI powered
team before you hire your first
employee. And that doesn't eliminate
every future hire. It actually gives you
the capabilities to start before you
need them. At AIS Live, I'll show you
how to build your own AI OS, a
personalized system of agents, tools,
and workflows that helps you operate a
real business. You'll discover the most
important AI agents for starting a
company, and how to install them for
free. You'll also see how an AIOS can
support content, marketing, sales,
operations, and even recruiting as your
company needs to keep growing. So, if
you want to start a highly profitable
business without building a huge team,
then click below for more details on AIS
Live. Now, it has similar elements,
right? But what I want you to pay
attention to here is all of the B-roll
that it went and collected from me. It
grabbed YouTube videos of mine. It went
ahead and it grabbed past AIS live, you
know, segments. So here's one with me
and Pat. We can go into here's like a
VIP session. Here's a video of me like
talking about my iOS and a second brain.
So it was able to use the context of
what the ad was about. Here's a session
with Hyper Agent and Alex. It used the
context of what we were talking about
and it actually put it inside so that
this doesn't just feel so much like
theory. It feels more real. and even
animated this logo here at the end,
which I thought was just beautiful
because it had to go to my Google Drive
to find the AIS Live logo. And I think
that this turned out really, really
nice. And I'll play one more for you
guys real quick, which was a call to
action that I gave Codeex. Real quick,
guys, just wanted to say if you're
enjoying this video and you're enjoying
the way that I teach, please consider
subscribing and joining my free school
community. The link for that is down in
the description. We're building a global
community of AI builders and
entrepreneurs and business owners. We're
almost at 450,000 members. We're almost
at half a million, which is super super
exciting. and it would just mean a lot
to me if you joined. We have a lot of
resources in here. We've got agent
skills. We've got every YouTube video
where I give away free resources. Like I
said, skills, guides, templates, docs,
GitHub repos. I give it all away in here
for completely free. We also have a
7-day challenge. We have a build your
AIOS course. We've got a lot of fun
stuff going on in here. Events,
certification programs, tons of cool
things that we're building towards. So,
if you're enjoying it, if you like the
way I teach, please definitely check it
out. Hope to see you guys in there.
Let's get back to the video. Now, what I
liked about this is this one felt very
clean, right? It wasn't super
fast-paced, super energetic. There's low
music, but once again, it's proving to
us that it can go grab screenshots, it
can crop them, and it can use context
about me and my business in order to
make these feel more relevant. It
grabbed all of these different, you
know, skills and docs, and it put them
in here in a really, really nice way. It
even went and screenshotted some of our
courses from the community. It grabbed,
you know, event assets and pictures and
videos, and it just made this call to
action feel so much more real, so much
more human. So, if you guys are getting
excited by that, go ahead, like I said,
to my free school community and grab all
of those skills to be able to replicate
those sorts of outputs. But now, let's
actually get started with building this.
Like, how do you actually do it? And I'm
going to walk through a real example
with you guys. If you guys remember the
intro from this video, I'm going to
build that out live right now with you
guys. So, the first thing that I want
you to do is you're going to open up a
new project. So, I would just open up a
new folder in your desktop or something.
And we'll just call this one for now.
I'm going to call this um hyperframes
demo. And that is the project that we're
going to be working inside of. So I've
got this folder on my desktop. Now I'm
going to come into here on the lefth
hand side and open up a new project. I'm
going to choose for this to be a local
project. I'm going to give this a name.
So Hyperframes demo. And then I'm going
to choose that actual folder so that
Codex can work inside of it. So that was
on my desktop and it was called
Hyperframes demo. Cool. So there's the
project. I'm going to select that and
open this up. So, when you open up a new
chat in this project, there's going to
be nothing in here. So, if I go over
here and I go to my files, there's
literally nothing here, but we're going
to start to fill this up with things
like video projects and different
renders and different files and things
like that. So, the first thing that I
want you to do is I want you to go to
this GitHub repo, which I will link in
the description. And this is called
Hyperframe. So, you're basically just
going to copy this URL for the
Hyperframes GitHub repo. You're going to
open up Codex, paste that in there, and
then basically just say, "Hey, Codex, I
need you to um basically pull in this
hyperframes repo so that I can um use it
to have you edit videos for me and
stuff. I need you to make sure that all
the dependencies are installed and
everything like that and, you know, grab
in some skills or things that you need
inside of this codeex project in order
to actually make this stuff useful." So,
that's the first step. You're going to
go ahead and shoot that off. Now, while
this is getting set up, let me talk
about the mindset and the idea of what
we're actually doing here when we're
editing videos with AI. So, there's a
few steps, right? And in this case, I'm
taking the example of we're giving it
some sort of footage and having it edit
it and animate it and things like that,
but it can also create things from
scratch. So, if you gave it um a rough
outline and you wanted just motion
graphics and like sizzle reels or like
SAS demos, it could do that 100%. But
that's not what I'm going to be focusing
on right now. You would just remove this
first step. So basically in my mind,
step one is you have footage and what
you need to do is you need to transcribe
it. And basically that means it needs to
find out all the text that you're saying
in that clip and exactly when it
happens, the exact second to the
millisecond of when you say certain
words so that it can sync it up with
different animations and different text
like subtitles for example. So
transcribing comes first. You can do
this with a free local thing that it can
set up like called whisper, but I
actually like to use 11 Labs for this.
So I'm going to show you how to set that
up as well. After you transcribe, then
the next thing that we want to do is we
probably want to cut. So, basically
having it cut out um you know, mistakes
or 5 seconds of silences and things like
that. So, that would be step two. Step
three then in my mind is to plan the
beats. That's kind of what it calls our
beats. So, beats are basically different
scenes. So, for example, with this reel,
like this install capability slide, this
is one beat and then like this is one
beat and this is one beat. Every
basically scene is a different beat. So
now what we like to do is we like to
have Astra, the model, read through the
text, understand the intent, and start
to plan out the beats of what's actually
going to go inside of this reel or
inside of this video. And then what it's
going to do is it's going to use its,
you know, skills, and it's going to use
hyperframes, and it's going to use other
tools like this in order to actually do
the generation of the HTML. It's
basically just creating HTML and it's
animating it. And that's what really
gives us all these 3D elements and it
gives us this text and it gives us what
we are basically looking at and
considering the motion graphics or the
motion design. And by the way, part of
planning the beats is like understanding
that there's going to be like, you know,
music that's going to sync to it and
sound effects and all of that is
basically coming into um this element of
planning. And the thing about it is we
have to have transcribed and cut all of
that first in order to be able to do
this properly. And then the last step
here is basically honestly it's kind of
a loop. So the last step is basically to
verify, meaning have the agent watch
through all of this again. It will watch
through it. It will take screenshots. It
will look at the transcript again. And
basically what we want to do is we're
going to do this loop of verifying and
then going back into here and using the
skills again and then verifying and then
using the skills again. So we get in
this loop of just going like this until
the agent is confident that everything
is in bounds and everything syncs
properly and everything feels how it
should. So that's kind of the flow.
Let's actually go get set up. So, we are
now inside of this project and it's
still getting everything set up. So,
what I want to show you what to do next
is we want to do um 11 Labs to
transcribe. So, you're going to go to a
new page. You're going to open up 11
Labs and create an account if you
haven't. You can get started on this for
like a five bucks a month plan, which it
it'll last you quite a while. So, you're
going to come in here and then what
you're going to do is you're going to go
on the bottom left to developers and
you're going to click on API keys right
here and you're going to go ahead and
create a new key. I'm just going to call
this um Astra demo. You can have this
expire. You could just leave this at
never. And then as far as restricting
the key, if you want to say, okay, this
key is literally only going to
transcribe stuff. That would be speech
to text. You could give it access to
speech to text. If you also want to give
it access to like sound effects and
music generation and image and video
generation, you can give it access to
other things as well. But right now, I'm
just going to start with just speech to
text because all we really need for this
endpoint is the um transcription. So,
I'm going to create this key. This gives
us basically a password. So, don't share
this with anybody. And I'm going to
delete this as soon as I'm done filming.
So, don't even think about it. But,
you're going to copy this to your
clipboard. You're going to go into
codeex and then we're going to come into
your files right over here. And you can
see now it's starting to build out some
folders and files and things like that.
And what you need is you need a file
called AENV which lets you store secrets
and passwords like your 11 Labs API key.
So all you have to do is just you can
chuck in a message even while it's
working here. And look, it actually
opened up a local host which is kind of
how we can see our video projects. This
is just you know it just lets us test
them and look at them and even like move
elements around and stuff which is
really really cool. But I'm just going
to close out of that because that was
just an example. But what I can do is
say when you do the transcriptions I
want you to use 11 labs. So, can you
please create me availabs
API key in there? And also make sure
that you include this in the agents.md
that says whenever you know Nate wants
you to transcribe a video, use 11 Labs
for that. So, the agents.mmd is this
file. This basically just explains how
the project works. So, right now,
because there's not much information in
there, it just has some very basic stuff
from hyperframes. But as you start to
learn more about the way you like to
edit videos and the way you like to
store your projects, you'll basically
want to come in here and update it with
certain information. So right here you
can see it says, "Okay, I will add that
rule into the agents.MD so that in the
future I'll stop the whisper setup which
is that local thing that I talked
about." Now nothing's wrong with
whisper, it's just slower. And so 11
Labs, yeah, you have to pay for it, but
it's much quicker and I like that speed
and it's not that expensive. So now ourv
has a placeholder for the 11 Labs API
key. So, what you're going to want to do
is just paste in your 11 Labs API key
right inside of here. And by the way, if
it's not letting you paste or type
anything in here, um, which it should,
but if it doesn't, then you can just go
into here and click on open in default
app. And for me, that opens up in my
notes. I can paste in the API key. Hit
save. And then, as you can see, it's
going to refresh live right inside of
here. All right. So, at this point, we
have enough information in here to
actually be able to use hyperframes. So,
I'm not going to use my skills that I
mentioned that I showed all of these
examples where I use my skills. I'm not
going to use these right now because I
just want to show you what this kind of
looks like at its core. But don't forget
that you can definitely grab those
skills and come in here and make these
things better. And so one thing that you
can do is you can give it a video file
and just say, "Hey, edit this for me.
You know, add motion graphics, make it
tell a story, blah blah blah." Or you
can be very specific, which is what I'm
going to do for this specific example.
So let me pull up the video that we're
going to be working with. It's right
here. It's called edit intro. So let me
actually open this up and we'll give it
a quick watch. This is just my natural
language. I can get all these crazy
motion graphics right here. And I get
all these insane animations over here as
well. I can have subtitles up here at
the bottom like you see. I can take my
face. I can put in the bottom right
corner. Okay. Anyway, so now you see
that I'm basically planning out what I
want to happen as it's happening. So
here's what I'm going to do. I'm going
to grab the file path of my um video.
I'm going to come back into here. I'm
going to do a slashgoal prompt for this,
which basically just means that I'm
setting a goal and it's going to keep
pursuing until it hits that goal. I'm
going to paste in the file path of that
video and I'm just going to start
instructing what I want to happen when I
want it to happen. But first, I have to
set up the loop of transcribing,
cutting, planning the beats, and then
it's going to go ahead and get to work.
But instead of planning the beats, I'm
kind of directing this a little bit
more. So, this is kind of like
plan/accept beats. But anyways, let me
show you what this is going to look like
as I instruct this thing.
So, I've just dropped in a video for
you. This is going to be an intro. So, I
need you to help me turn this into a
super premium and polished edited video.
So, the first thing you need to do is I
want you to transcribe the video because
we need all of the beats and all the
motion graphics to sync exactly when I
say them. And then I need you to cut out
anything if there's mistakes or if
there's um you know, silence. There
shouldn't really be like a second or a
half second of silence. I want this to
feel fast-paced. After you've done those
two things, it's time to start actually
animating this video. So, let me tell
you what I'm looking for when it comes
to the animations. So, I start off this
intro by saying something like, "Isn't
it crazy that I can use just my natural
language to get all these crazy motion
graphics over here and all these crazy
animations over here?" What I want to
happen then is I want this whole vibe of
this video to be very, very like Apple
style motion design. So, like liquid
glass, clean animations, um, and they
feel very professional. So, when I say
motion graphics over here, I believe
that my hand was on it was pointing to
the left side of the screen. So on the
left third of the screen, I want them
from top down, sort of like my hands are
creating these motion graphics. I want
them to come into screen and just make
them, you know, against like some sort
of liquid glass card where we see three
different types of motion graphics.
Maybe like cards and documents moving
around or um laptop screens and charts
and elements that are being like
animated and things like that. Just make
things over here that are impressive and
that tell a visual story. And then
similarly when I go into the insane
animations over here as well that's on
the right side of the screen. So same
thing I want them to come in from top
down like I'm drawing them in. I want
these to be 3D. So I want these to be
against some sort of um maybe little
overlay in the back so that we can see
them against the background just like a
subtle dark overlay. And these should be
3D. So um they should maybe look like
they're spinning. They should have
shadows. They should have depth. And
these can just be 3D like letters or 3D
um animations and I don't know like
symbols that are moving. Just make
these, you know, subtle and
professional, but they should certainly
give some sort of like wow factor. And
for those two beats, I want them to stay
on the screen while I'm talking about
them. And then I want them to leave the
screen or sort of like fade away at the
same moment. So the motion graphics on
the left come in first, animations on
the right come in second, and then they
leave the screen at the same time. The
next section is pretty simple. When I
say I can have subtitles appearing at
the bottom as you see, I just want a
super super clean um overlay at the
bottom of the screen with subtitles,
they shouldn't cover um my face. So,
they should be sort of near the lower
third. And if you could just have the
words like subtly highlighted with maybe
like the words are white, but they're
highlighted in blue when I'm actually
saying them. So, make sure they're
synced exactly to the transcript when
I'm saying them. Now, in the next
section, I go on to say, you know, I can
take my face and I can move it to the
bottom right corner or um the top left.
And what I want you to do for that is I
want you to take my face cam and sort of
shrink it into like a um a vertical
rounded crop. So, you kind of just bring
in the left and right sides to keep me
centered. And you make it rounded crop
with a drop shadow. And you put it
against this background, which is the
full screen background. And so here what
I'm doing is I just pasted in this
picture which I like to use as uh my
background in some YouTube videos. And I
want you to make that background 50%
opacity so it's a little bit darker. And
then for the next part when I say I can
play you guys these um clips from my
YouTube videos, I want you to go to my
YouTube video directory locally which
I'll give you the file path too. So I
will just copy in this file path real
quick right there. What I want you to do
is just grab a few of my most recent
videos, maybe like four or six, and I
want you to sort of fan them out, like
animate the process of you fanning them
out, and have these be 3D with like a
little bit of a drop shadow, and they're
sort of like rotating and swiveling back
and forth just to create a really cool
effect. But I want them to actually be
playing throughout. I don't want them
just be static images of the videos. I
want you to just play, you know, all of
them are sort of actually playing at the
same time. And then to end off the
video, what I want you to do is
basically against that background I gave
you, if you could bring my main face
cam, sort of align it on the left side
of the screen, but make it bigger so it
kind of touches the top and bottom of
the screen, but we should still see the
rounded crop and the drop shadow. And
then on the right side of the screen, we
can just have some other text and other
motion graphics that tell a story based
on what I'm saying. So like um you know,
you don't have to be technical, you
don't have to have used codecs before,
you don't have to have a video editing
background. if you could just make
little icons and animate them in a fun
way to tell that story. And then at the
end, you know, it says like, "Hey, I
don't want to waste any time. Let's just
get straight straight into the video."
Do the exact same thing there. And
that's going to pretty much be the end
of this intro. After you have then done
all of that, I just want you to make
sure it looks good. I want you to sort
of like verify it by taking some
screenshots and looking through, making
sure that the beats actually sync to the
text that I'm reading out and make sure
that um everything's in bounds and
everything looks professional and it's
giving off the quality that you want it
to. I'm not looking for a PC or a
version one. I'm looking for a finished
product ready to go here. Out of breath
a little bit. So, that was a massive
prompt, right? That was me being super
super specific about what I'm actually
looking for here. And that's kind of
what this looks like to start. The way
that I got to all of these skills that I
now use for YouTube videos, lessons,
reals, ads, is because I did that so
many times. And now if you get an output
here that you really, really like, you
say, "Cool, that was awesome. Turn that
into a skill." And then next time, you
don't have to give such a big prompt.
You basically just say, "Hey, edit this
video. Use this skill." And then when it
comes back, if you have feedback, say,
"Hey, I didn't like this. Make sure you
do this next time." And then update the
skill, too. So, what I just did is
really the hardest it'll ever be. And
then it's always just about iterating on
those skills. So, I'm just going to go
ahead and let this cook a little bit. I
will check in with you guys when this
one comes back with the first version.
And hopefully it's what you saw in the
beginning of this video. Okay. So, I
have not yet watched this, but you can
see that this went from the original
being, what was this? A little over a
minute, a minute and 5 seconds to now
being cut down to 28 seconds. Let's go
ahead and give this a watch and see how
this looks. Isn't it crazy that with
just my natural language, I can get all
of these crazy motion graphics right
here? And I can get all of these insane
animations over here as well. I can have
subtitles appearing at the bottom like
you see. I can take my face and I can
put it in the bottom right corner or I
can bring it up to the top left corner.
I can even play you guys clips of a
bunch of my different YouTube videos
right here in this sort of 3D fashion.
So, by the end of this video, you will
know exactly how to actually do this
even if you've never really used codecs
before or you've never edited videos
before. So, I don't want to waste any of
your time. Let's just get straight into
this video. Okay, not bad. Not bad for a
first pass. Um, you can see how my very
specific prompting obviously benefited
us here. I think that these look good,
right? Like we get some 3D animations,
we get some motion graphics. I like it.
I think that's a good way to start. I do
think maybe we need something more in
the first two seconds. Yeah, I think we
should add something right there in the
first two seconds just to make it more
engaging. But the other thing I noticed
is right here. It's playing videos,
which is good, but they're like inter
overlapping with each other, right? So
they it's not realistic. What we need to
do is make this feel more legit. And
also, I want to make this text bigger. I
don't think that text is big enough. And
I think this looks fine. This is all
simple. Nice little animation as well.
Basically, that's my feedback. So, let
us shoot off prompt number two. I'm
going to once again do another slash
goal prompt. Awesome. So, I mean, that
was 18 minutes. That was a really good
first pass, but let's do another version
here. What I want is a couple things.
First of all, in the first two seconds,
I want you to get creative here. Do
something that feels on brand
to make the first two seconds more
engaging. I'm not sure I want like a
full screen cutaway and I don't want
anything that's going to lay on top of
my face, but you know, I start off the
video by like, isn't it crazy that with
just my natural language, some sort of
animation, some sort of motion graphic,
make that a little bit more emotional?
Just do something right away to sort of
like hook the viewer in. Now, besides
that, the only other changes I need are
in the part where you show my YouTube
videos, you show the four. I like how
these look like they're 3D and they have
depth, but if you could make this more
realistic because they clearly are like
cutting through each other almost like
it's not realistic. We need this to be
more like the physics of it need to feel
better. So, if you could just maybe make
them thicker and make sure that they're
they're fanned out behind each other
rather than like cutting through each
other, that would be great. And then the
text on that screen, it says like your
videos or something. um if you could
just make that larger because that text
was pretty small. I want it to be bigger
and easier to read. But besides that,
everything else I thought looked really
good and it matched the transcript
really well also. So make those changes
please and then let me know when you're
done. So that is prompt number two going
off as another goal. Now you can see
that this is the actual hyperframe
studio that it created for us. Um this
is at 107. Let's just reset that. And
what's cool is I can literally move
things in here. So I can actually take
this element and I could increase the
text size over here. I think font this
is where I would do it. I could change
this to what, like 80, and see how that
looks. So, it would reload and now I can
just sort of manipulate this stuff right
from here, which is pretty cool. You
know, you can move stuff around and um
you can see there's even different
elements for the actual like 3D scene
and the actual video inside. So, I'm not
going to mess with that right now. I
honestly don't use that interface too
much. But if you're editing a really
long video, let's say it's like a
10-minute video, and you just want to be
able to like tweak one thing really
subtly, it's probably easier to come in
here, make a little tweak, like just
move this over and then export it rather
than having to do the prompt layer
again. So, it's really nice that
Hyperframes gives you this local host
environment as well. But for something
as simple as what we're doing, I just
wanted to shoot off another natural
language prompt. So, I will check in
with you guys once this one has finished
up. All right, so that took 10 minutes
now and V2 has come back. Let me go
ahead and open this up full screen and
we'll give it a watch. Isn't it crazy
that with just my natural language, I
can get all of these crazy motion
graphics right here and I can get all of
these insane animations over here as
well. I can have subtitles appearing at
the bottom like you see. I can take my
face and I can put it in the bottom
right corner or I can bring it up to the
top left corner and I can even play you
guys clips of a bunch of my different
YouTube videos right here in this sort
of 3D fashion. Okay, so this was much
better. The text got larger and this
feels more 3D and it also just feels
like, you know, it just looks better.
And so right here, this is pretty much
the only section where I didn't tell it
exactly what I wanted. And this is what
it came up with. I don't honestly love
it. But for now, I'm just going to keep
it in because I told it I didn't want a
full screen takeaway, which would have
meant it created its own animation to be
the full screen. But actually, let's
just see what that would look like if I
just shoot off that quick prompts real
quick and say, "Awesome. Now, can you
create me one more version where in the
first two seconds before you cut into
like the motion graphics and everything,
let's see what this would look like if
you did a full screen takeaway." So, it
would be the full screen is animated um
against some sort of, you know,
background that feels on brand with the
rest of the intro and maybe the text is
sort of comes in in an animated way that
says, "Isn't it crazy?" So, anyways,
just going to shoot that off. This
really shouldn't take long at all, but
just to show you guys that it can also
do things like, you know, a full screen
cutaway and animate it in that way, too.
So, I'll show you guys that in just a
sec. All right, so that one came back
and it's done. And I have a feeling that
it's basically just going to be super
simple right here. I'll play it from
this interface. Isn't it crazy that with
just my natural language, I can get all
of these crazy motion graphics right
here and I can get all of these Cool.
So, that is looking good. We can see
basically all this did was just add some
very simple animated text that came in
here. It had a little bit of layering as
well with these little liquid glass
looking cards and it kept the background
consistent to what we actually used
later over here. So, I thought that's
pretty good. Anyways, guys, at this
point, we've set up the project. You've
set up something to transcribe if you
decided to use 11 Labs and you
understand now the loop that we actually
go through in order to do all this. I
didn't dive too much into this actual
interface and how you control it, but
like I said, it's very, very intuitive
once you get in here and it's a nice
touch by Hyperframes. So, don't forget
if you want to get this student kit that
has all of the skills that you need to
build these sorts of reels and videos,
you can download this for completely
free by going to my free school
community. The link is in the
description. You'll go to classroom and
click on AI skills and it will be in
there. But guys, that is going to do it
for today. So, I really hope that you
enjoyed the video, you learned something
new. And if you did, please give it a
like. It helps me out a ton. And if you
want to see other stuff you can do with
codecs and with GBD6 Astra, then
definitely check out this playlist that
I'll link right up here. I hope to see
you guys over there, but thanks for
watching till the end and I'll see you
in the next one.